[{"id": 2416, "question": "John and Booby joined a wholesale company together just after graduation from college the same year. Both worked very hard. After several years, however, the boss promoted Bobby to the position of manager but John remained an ordinary employee . John could not take it any more, so he sent his resignation and complained that the boss did not value hard working workers but only promoted those who said good words of him. The boss knew that John worked very hard for the years. He thought for a moment and said, \"Thank you for telling me, but I have a request. I hope you will do one more thing for our company before you leave. Perhaps you will change your mind and take back your resignation.\" John agreed. The boss asked him to go and find out anyone selling watermelons in the market. John went a...\n\nQ: From what Bobby did, we can see that he was promoted only because   _  .", "options": ["he was a more concerned businessman", "he knew how to do business", "he was more experienced at work", "he knew details about the watermelon market"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1717, "question": "Healthy relationships are fun and make you feel good about yourself. The relationships that you make in your teenage years will be a special pan of your life. They will teach you some of the most important lessons about who you are. This may help you understand different kinds of relationships, what makes each relationship special, and how to communicate in a positive way. What makes a relationship healthy? Communication and Sharing: The most important part of any healthy relationship between two people is being able to talk and listen to each other. You and the other person can find out what your common interests are. You can share your feelings with the other person and trust that he or she will be there to listen to you and support you. In healthy relationships, people don't lie. Commun...\n\nQ: The passage implies that   _  .", "options": ["it's easy to establish a good relationship with someone", "you don't need to give anything to make relationships healthy", "healthy relationships need money, time, energy and care", "mutual respect and trust lead to strong relationships"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2568, "question": "When Steve Jobs was born on Febuary24,1955, in San Francisco , California, his unmarried mother decided to put him for adoption because she wanted a girl. So in the middle of the night, his mother called a lawyer named Paul Jobs and said, \"We have an unexpected baby boy; do you want him?\" But his mother told his future parents to promise that they would send Jobs to college. After Steve Jobs graduated from high school, he went to college but decided to drop out because it was so expensive that he had to sleep on the floor in his friends' rooms. At 20, he and a friend(Steve Wozniak) started a company in a garage on April 1, 1976. Jobs named their company ----Apple in memory of a happy summer he had spent as an orchard in Oregon. After 10 years of hard time and failures, starting from two ki...\n\nQ: Steve Jobs didn't finish his college education because he   _  .", "options": ["wanted to start a company.", "had financial problems.", "took no interest in his major.", "hated to share rooms with his friends."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 188, "question": "Boys' schools are the perfect place to teach young men to express their emotions and involve them in activities such as art, dance and music. Far from the traditional image of a culture of aggressive masculinity ,the absence of girls gives boys the chance to develop without pressure to be consistent to a stereotype ,a US study says. Boys at single-sex schools were said to be more likely to get involved in cultural and artistic activities that helped develop their abilities to express their emotions,rather than feeling they had to obey to the\"boy code\"of hiding their emotions to be a\"real man\". The findings of the study are against the received wisdom that boys do better when taught alongside girls. Tony Little,headmaster of Eton,warned that boys were being ignored by the British education ...\n\nQ: The author believes that a single-sex school would  _  .", "options": ["force boys to hide their emotions to be\"real men\"", "help to form masculine aggressiveness in boys", "encourage boys to express their emotions more freely", "naturally place emphasis on the traditional image of a man to boys"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1542, "question": "Ban Fur? Then Why Not Leather? Much to the displeasure of some local businesses, the City Council in West Hollywood, California, voted without opposition last week to ban the sale of fur products. Should laws be involved in this issue? Is it unfair to ban sales of fur, but not sales of leather and hides ? Animals Do Not Have Rights By Tibor R. Machan My view is that animals do not have basic rights. It is a matter of ethics and not of the laws of human societies. If animals had such rights as human beings do, they would have to be held responsible for killing fellow animals in the wild. That way of thinking about animals makes a category mistake. Using animals, including their fur or organs, to improve people's lives is acceptable. A Small Step Against Cruelty By Kate Carter Both fur and l...\n\nQ: What is Kate Carter's opinion about wearing fur and wearing leather?", "options": ["Both are decided by the meat industry.", "There is little distinction between them.", "Wearing fur is generally more acceptable.", "Wearing leather is cheaper than wearing fur."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 965, "question": "The skin which covers the tips of the fingers and thumbs is crossed by numerous ridges arranged in different patterns. These patterns are permanent from birth and remain exactly the same throughout a person's life, even when the skin becomes wrinkled and cracked as a result of old age. Such patterns are never passed on from parents to children, and no one in the world has the same patterns as anyone else. Even identical twins have different sets of fingerprints. As a result, fingerprints offer a most useful and _ way of identifying people. Any ridged part of the hand and the foot may be used as a means of identification, but finger impressions are usually preferred since they can be taken easily and quickly. Fingerprints are classified in the ways: by general shapes and contours , by the f...\n\nQ: According to this passage, the true statement about human fingerprints is that   _  .", "options": ["people's fingerprints sometimes can be passed on from parents to children", "people's fingerprints are unique but identical twins may have the same fingerprints", "using fingerprints is the only way to identify people", "people's fingerprints will not change in all their lives"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3163, "question": "One night recently , I was driving down a two-lane highway at about 60 miles an hour . A car approached from the opposite direction at about the same speed . As we passed each other , I caught the other driver's eye for only a second . I wondered whether he might be thinking , as I was , how dependent we were on each other at that moment . I was relying on him not to fall asleep , not to be put off by a phone conversation, not to cross over into my lane and bring my life to a sudden end . Though we had never spoken a word to each other , he relied on me in just the same way . Multiplied a million times over, I believe that is the way the world works . At some level , we all depend upon one another . Sometimes that dependence requires us simply not to do something like crossing over the dou...\n\nQ: The need for cooperation increases because  _  .", "options": ["peoples' fates can't be controlled by themselves", "the SARS virus spread quickly", "terrorism can happen everywhere", "the world has become smaller"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3023, "question": "For years we have been dieting strictly after the year-end overeating, afraid that when summer. comes, the bigger size we have accumulated will betray how we ate. Now scientists say, it's a little bug that causes obesity . As the holiday season with its abundant feasting arrives, millions of food lovers are keeping an eye on their figures. But scientists have found that weight gain is not about too much Christmas turkey or hot chocolates, but some bacteria in your guts . Chinese scientists recently discovered a type ofbacteria in guts that may be to blame for obesity. A research team led by Zhao Liping, a professor in Shanghai, has identified a precise link between a particular kind ofbacteria and unusual weight gain. \"The endotoxin released by the bacterium can activate a gene that helps ...\n\nQ: The patient finally lost 51.4 kg of his weight after   _  .", "options": ["35 percent of his gut bacteria were killed", "the amount of gut bacteria was decreased", "he had a special kind ofoperation", "his fatty liver had disappeared"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2892, "question": "From Chengdu to Jiuzhaigou, you can travel along the East Line not only the other line going past Dujiangyan and Wenchuan. Take a regular bus from Chengdu Chengbei Bus Station from 9:00 to 16:30. It only takes about three hours to Jiangyou. The ticket is CNY50.00 net per person. Up along Fujiang River, you will pass the second largest city in Sichuan, Mianyang and enjoy the picturesque scenery. There is bus available to the destination from 6:30 to 13:30 in Mianyang Pingzheng Bus Station,The one way ticket is about CNY95.00 net per person. In this case, you can not get stop at Jiangyou and Pingwu. This is one option for you. In Jiangyou, visit the Former Residence of Li Bai, the famous poet in Tang Dynasty. If time permits, you can also take a look at the Doutuan Mountain, which is famous ...\n\nQ: Where is this passage likely to appear?", "options": ["An advertisement of local hotels.", "A travel guide for foreign travelers.", "A geography book of Sichuan Province", "A newspaper for English learners."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2079, "question": "The United States government has decided that food from cloned cattle, pigs and goats is safe to eat. The Food and Drug Administration also says it found no risks in meat and milk from cloned animals. The F.D.A. looked at studies for several years before it announced its decision in a final report this month. The United States Department of Agriculture supported the findings. But it says time is needed to clear the way for marketing meat and milk from clones. The F.D.A. will not require any product to be registered as coming from clones. A producer would need to label a product \"clone-free\". The agency says that could be misunderstood because the food is not different from other food. But activists argue that the F.D.A. based its decision on incomplete research into possible risks. The Cen...\n\nQ: Where can you probably see the passage?", "options": ["In a novel.", "In a newspaper.", "In a travel leaflet.", "In a notice on the wall."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2690, "question": "Teresa was born in Yugoslavia on August 27,1910. Her parents were Albanians and member of the Roman Catholic Church. When she was seven years old, her father was murdered. She decided not to be filled with hate because of this tragedy . Instead, she would seek a life of love. This ambition led her to Ireland where she became a nun at the age of eighteen. After only one year of training, she was sent to India to teach in a school called Loretto House, where the students were mostly from rich Indian families. After 15 years there, she left her duties as a teacher to \"follow Christ into the slums .\" Her heart led her away from the rich to the needs of the poor. She was then 36 years old. Teresa no longer was affiliated with the Irish nuns who sent her to Loreto House but worked independently....\n\nQ: Why did she leave her duties as a teacher after 15 years in Loretto House?", "options": ["To be a teacher was too tired", "The students in Loretto House were rich.", "She was tired of teaching.", "The poor in the slums needed her care."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2601, "question": "Eighteen-year-old Dana Kiger is happily running after balls on the soccer field. But not long ago, she couldn't remember her love of the game, her parents' faces or even her name. At 16, the Tennessee honor student and star athlete was hit from behind while playing in a soccer game. She fell to the ground, her head striking the hard ground. The blow knocked out nearly all of Kiger's memories. With no physical injury or unusual change in her brain, doctors thought Kiger's memory would return in a few days. But it did not. And two and a half years later, it still hasn't. Kiger--who has no memory of her family, her childhood or her life before her injury--has had to create new memories, restart relationships and relearn old skills. \"The only thing I had ...I could walk, write, but I didn't kn...\n\nQ: What would be the best title for this text?", "options": ["Parents Worried about Child's Injury", "Soccer Injury Wipeed Out Teen's Memory", "Teen Suffered from Bad Memory", "Doctors Helped Teen Recreate Memories"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2695, "question": "Every day we meet people in a number of business and social situations. And the way we meet and greet them creates an impression. It's important to do so in a proper way, no matter whether you are introducing yourself to someone, or introducing two people. To keep you aware of this, we have gathered tips on how to make a proper introduction. *Always stand when making an introduction. When you are seated and someone comes up to greet you, make the effort to stand up. By doing this, you show respect for yourself and for the other person. *Always keep eye contact while making an introduction. Many people are not aware of the value of this simple action. When you make eye contact, you are giving a confident image. *Always introduce a person of lesser authority to one of greater authority. The ...\n\nQ: If you forget the other person's name, you'd better   _  .", "options": ["ask him/her directly", "apologize first and then ask him/her", "shake hands with the person and reintroduce yourself", "consider his age first"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1383, "question": "Do you want to be a successful person? Would you like to know how successful people usually think and what drives them? Here I am going to tell you the key to success that successful people share. First of all, successful people never blame someone or something outside of themselves for their failure to move ahead. They realize that their future lies in their own hands. They understand that they can't control things in life, such as nature, the past and other people. At the same time, they are well aware that they can control their own thoughts and actions. They take responsibility for their life. Perhaps what most separates successful people from others is that they live life \"on purpose\" --- they are doing what they believe they are put here to do. In their opinion, having a purpose in t...\n\nQ: According to the passage, to be successful,   _  .", "options": ["you should set up a realistic goal", "you should know your strengths and weaknesses", "you shouldn't blame others for your failure", "you shouldn't waste time"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1067, "question": "The Opening of the Book Nook Saturday, October 4, 10 AM to 10 PM You will not want to miss the opening of your new neighborhood bookstore! Located at 2289 Main Street, the Book Nook is within walking distance of schools, many homes and businesses. Come and check out the Book Nook on Saturday! Activities will include: * Live music by local musicians * One Book-of-the-Month Club membership giveaway Wide Selection The Book Nook has three floors with books of all kinds---any kind you could want. If we do not have the book you are looking for, we can specially order it for you. You will have it in your hands within two days! Reading Nooks We are proud of our children's reading area on the first floor, as well as our teenagers' nook on the second floor. Come for the activities and stay for a whi...\n\nQ: What can we learn about the Book Nook?", "options": ["It is a well-located bookstore.", "Any interesting books can be found right here.", "It is open from 10 AM to 10 PM every day.", "The third floor is specially designed for children."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 975, "question": "Schouten University is a highly respected online education provider offering officially-recognized degree programs across the globe. Our mission is to provide students with a high-quality mixed learning MBA program and personal coaching to help them to become world-class managers. MBA with Unique Skills & Personal Development Program Students will benefit from 30 years of soft skills training experience from Schouten & Nielsen, the leading soft skills training institute in Europe. To become an effective manager, theory alone is not enough, and being able to put theory into practice is more important today than ever before. With the Schouten University MBA program you will have the unique opportunity to develop such soft skills as influencing skills, leadership skills, communication skills ...\n\nQ: Most graduates of Schouten University will work in the field of   _  .", "options": ["education", "military", "medicine", "business"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 926, "question": "Of course, you know that getting a gift for your dad is a must every Father's Day. Perhaps last year you got him a tie he always wanted, or a watch that had the year of his marriage engraved upon it. Yes, all of those gifts were great, but if this year you'd like to get him a gift that he'll be able to hold onto for a long time without breaking your bank, you should consider making a gift yourself. For example, a keepsake box that holds precious keepsakes can be a simple yet timeless gift. Find a box. It can be a cigar box or hat box, but it really has to be strong and long-lasting. Decorate the inside and outside .of your box with paints, ribbons , fabric and other materials.\" Include some of your personal items that best _ your relationship with your dad or a memory that he and you share...\n\nQ: What is the text mainly about?", "options": ["What to do on Father's Day.", "How to choose Father's Day gifts.", "How to remember Father's Day.", "How to make a meaningful Father's Day gift."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3232, "question": "This Monday,the nation will start to celebrate Presidents' Day,just seven days before George Washington's birthday.Everyone agrees that day is a holiday,but is it just to celebrate George Washington's Birthday? What about Abraham Lincoln? Some government offices call it Presidents' Day.Others say the holiday is officially Washington's Birthday.Confused yet? George Washington was elected the country's first President on April 30,1789.Soon after,Americans began publicly celebrating his birthday.Presidential historians say the actual date of George Washington's birth is February 11,1732.But a change in the calendar system 20 years later shifted all dates,making Washington's birthday February 22,which is now well accepted.In 1879.Congress made Washington's birthday an official federal holiday....\n\nQ: The President's Day was originally designed to honor  _  .", "options": ["George Washington", "Abraham Lincoln", "all presidents", "the Civil War"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2623, "question": "The story of Juno and Lucas is one of the most touching stories about the amazing relationship between humans and their companion animals. Juno is a Belgian Malinois . The dog was beautiful but was given up by its owners, as they did not want to take on the responsibility. Lucas, a little boy, had a strange illness, a condition that stops the body's ability to process enzymes .As his life continues, he will lose the ability to speak and his physical and mental abilities will degrade till he is left in a vegetative state. The average life expectancy for the patients is 15 years. Chester, the boy's father, wanted his child to enjoy his life on earth as much as possible and looked into getting a service dog for the child. However, Lucas wasn't a good candidate due to his deteriorating abiliti...\n\nQ: Chester got the dog Juno by   _  .", "options": ["asking for help from the police force", "donating a lot of money", "picking it up near the house", "searching on the Internet"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1156, "question": "What does the future hold for the problem of housing? A good deal depends, of course, on the meaning of \"future\". If one is thinking in terms of science fiction and the space age, it is at least possible to assume that man will have solved such trivial and earthly problems as housing. Writers of science fiction, from H.G. Wells onwards, have had little to say on the subject. They have conveyed the suggestion that men will live in great comfort, with every imaginable apparatus to make life smooth, healthy and easy, if not happy. But they have not said what his house will be made of. Perhaps some new building material, as yet unimagined, will have been discovered or invented at least. One may be certain that bricks and mortar(,) will long have gone out of fashion. But the problems of the nex...\n\nQ: The writer is sure that in the distant future   _  .", "options": ["bricks and mortar will be replaced by some other building material.", "a new building material will have been invented.", "bricks and mortar will not be used by people who want their house to be fashionable.", "a new way of using bricks and mortar will have been discovered."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1403, "question": "China's former volleyball star Lang Ping has been invited to coach the US women's national team for the Beijing 2008 Olympics. But China's sports media said the offer would be difficult to accept. Lang, who is presently coaching a club team in Italy's professional volleyball league, told sina.com that she was considering the offer by the US Volleyball Association. \"Right now I'm still considering their offer but I will answer them soon,\"Lang said. \"If I don't take the job, I have to give them enough time to find someone else.\" Lang, 45,won Olympic gold in 1984. She later coached the Chinese women to silver at the 1996 Atlanta Olympics and the 1998 World Championships. She has also coached at New Mexico University in the United States where her daughter was born and lives. The reaction in t...\n\nQ: Form the text, we can learn   _  .", "options": ["Lang Ping has accepted the offer", "Chen Zhonghe has got into trouble", "all of the Chinese media support Lang Ping", "Lang Ping is thinking the US offer over"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2672, "question": "\"Wake up. Alicia is waiting for you outside,\" my mother called from the kitchen. My mother didn't like me going for this weekend to my friend's house in the mountains. \"I trust you, but I don't trust the people out there,\" she said seriously. \"I'm going to be fine,\" were my last words before closing the door of the Jeep. The vehicle went along the dusty road and my mother grew smaller in the distance. The trip over the rough road was uncomfortable. It was scary to climb the steep hills surrounded by great pines. After a long trip we finally arrived at the house. From the moment I got there I knew I would forever love the house. It was decorated like an old country home. My room was small, yet set up nicely. That night I went to sleep early, not because I didn't want to continue my search, ...\n\nQ: The purpose of the trip for the author is to  _  .", "options": ["enjoy the quiet and beautiful nature", "continue her search for special things", "give herself a chance to think alone", "go hiking in the mountains with her friend"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1389, "question": "Many years ago, when I was fresh out of school and working in Denver, I was driving to my parents' home in Missouri for Christmas. I stopped at a gas station about 50 miles from Oklahoma City, where I was planning to stop and visit a friend. While I was standing in line at the cash register , I said hello to an older couple who were also paying for gas. I took off, but had gone only a few miles when black smoke poured from the back of my car. I stopped and wondered what I should do. A car pulled up behind me. It was the couple I had spoken to at the gas station. They said they would take me to my friend's We chatted on the way into the city, and when I got out of the car, the husband gave me his business card. I wrote him and his wife a thank-you note for helping me. Soon afterward, I rece...\n\nQ: By telling his own experiences, the author tries to show  _  .", "options": ["how to write a thank-you letter", "how to deal with car problems", "the kind-heartedness of older people", "the importance of expressing thanks"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2713, "question": "Without any previous notice, a documentary dominated headlines and social websites over the weekend. Under the Dome, a 103-minute documentary self-funded by former CCTV news anchor Chai Jing was released on video-sharing websites in China on Feb 28. It has rapidly pushed the public awareness about air pollution and encouraged people to join in efforts to make a difference. Chai, 39, said she started the work out of her \"personal clashes\" with smog after she gave birth to a daughter. \"I sealed tight all the windows. I started every day by checking the air pollution index,\" Chai said. Millions of other people are also doing the same. While they stop there, Chai goes deeper. \"I don't want to live in this way. 1 need to find out where the smog comes from and what on earth is going on.\" Over a ...\n\nQ: what's the author's attitude towards the film?", "options": ["positive", "objective", "negative", "indifferent"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3210, "question": "People want action on noise, a recent public meeting in Brisbane showed.Some want technical improvements such as quieter air conditioners or better sound barriers around major roads.Others want tougher laws to restrict noise from building sites or to require owners to take responsibility for barking dogs.But the highest priority was a noise complaints system that works. Brisbane City Council receives more complaints about noise than all other problems put together.So it conducted a survey and found that about half its residents are upset by noise in one form or another -traffic, mowers, pool pumps, air conditioners or loud parties.This inspired the Council to bring together more than 100 citizens one evening to talk through a range of options. The meeting found the present regulatory syste...\n\nQ: What was the author's attitude towards the industry awards for quieter equipment?", "options": ["Suspicious.", "Positive.", "Enthusiastic.", "Indifferent."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 327, "question": "How will you celebrate New Year's Eve? By having a party with your classmates? Going to the karaoke for a singing competition? Many people around the world celebrate the day. Let's have a look at what people in other countries do. In the United States, thousands of people jam into Times Square in New York to welcome in the new year at midnight. The change from New Year's Eve and New Year's Day is very exciting. People count down the seconds to welcome the new day as the New Year ball slowly gets down and lights up the area. In Spain, when the clock strikes midnight, everyone eats 12 grapes. They eat one grape for each toll to bring good luck for the next 12 months of the new year. In Scotland, fireworks are set off in front of the Edinburgh Castle. Immediately after midnight, people sing A...\n\nQ: In Scotland, you will probably see   _  .", "options": ["the famous poet Robert Burns sings the Auld Lang Syne", "most people wear white clothes", "people go for a singing competition", "fireworks set off in front of the Edinburgh Castle"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2663, "question": "Try imagining what the world will be like in the year 3000. Some serious thinkers are starting to imagine just that. Bart: I don't know that present-day electronic chips are, but some sort of chips -- I'd guess maybe plastic. Our three-pound brain is definitely a wonder, perhaps the greatest wonder of natural biology. In this coming century, we'll be re-engineering the brain a piece at a time, first with implants and finally engineering an complete replacement. There's no question that in the distant future we'll play the music of the mind on instruments different from the current ones. So, yes, chips are our destiny . Edward: In 3000 perhaps the biggest difference from today is that there will be no more men. Females can have female children, without any need for men. In about ten years, ...\n\nQ: What does Bart refer to by saying \"chips are our destiny\"?", "options": ["Chips are our last choice in the future.", "Chips are on the way to controlling mind.", "Chips are the production of future technology.", "Chips are the implants in the distant future."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2993, "question": "Almost 70 percent of Chinese middle school students have serious problems with their parents, the Beijing Morning Post quoted a survey as saying. The survey showed 6.62 percent of the surveyed students are afraid of their parents while 13.13 percent of them dislike their parents and 56.28 percent were extremely disgusted with or even hate their parents. Only 4.75 percent of the young people surveyed said they like their parents. The recently conducted survey among 3,000 middle school students in a Beijing district asked questions about their attitude toward their parents and family education, the paper said. For many families, conflict between parents and children center on the student's school grades, their weight and their friends. The survey showed that parental influence over children ...\n\nQ: What is the central conflict between parents and children in many families?", "options": ["Family violence and divorce.", "Parents' old fashioned ideas.", "Interference in a child's privacy.", "Students' school grades, weight and friends."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1902, "question": "Students usually have two long holidays a year, but have you heard elephants have holidays? The Indian elephants from a temple are sent on a north-long holiday with massages and baths to relax. The 64 elephants will be fed with a lot of food, enough for them to put on 700~800 pounds. A temple veterinarian said that those Indian elephants would be treated after spending a month walking on roads, living on leaves and bananas and giving shows during lots of temple festivals. Their daily diet includes special rice and other special food, which are very _ and can make them healthy and strong. All of these are made by professional people. This treatment will also calm them down ahead of a busy work schedule in upcoming events later in the year where they are the main attractions. The special hol...\n\nQ: The elephants can do the following during their holiday EXCEPT  _  .", "options": ["eating delicious food", "giving performances", "taking a shower", "having a massage"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 957, "question": "The Jungle Book Lost in the jungles of India as a child and adopted into a family of wolves, Mowgli is brought up on a diet of Jungle Law, loyalty, and fresh meat from the kill. Regular adventures with his friends and enemies in the jungles improve this child's strength and cleverness and stir every reader's imagination. Price: $ 7.79 ISBN-13: 978-1613820742 Average Customer Review: A Stolen Life The first work of its kind--Jaycee Dugard's personal life story, her own story of being kidnapped in 1991. When Jaycee was eleven years old, she was kidnapped from a school bus stop. She was missing for more than eighteen years, and gave birth to two daughters during her imprisonment . Price: $ 19.79 ISBN-13: 978-1442344983 Average Customer Review: While We're Far Apart Five-time Christy Award win...\n\nQ: What makes the book The Fashion Police distinguish itself from others?", "options": ["It wins the award Christy Award five times.", "It is a great book on violence and family education.", "It is nominated Best Novel with Romantic Elements 2010.", "It has many elements borrowed from stories of true policemen."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 373, "question": "My friend Mike was shaking his head in disbelief. \"That young woman who just waited on me,\" he said, pointing to an employee of the fast food restaurant where we were eating, \"had to call someone over to help her count change. The cash register showed her I needed 99 cents, but she couldn't figure out how to count out the coins.\" I understood Mike's concern. What we have done is to create several generations of individuals most of whom have no idea how to reason; how to do simple math; how to do research; or, finally, how to be creative . The reason for this is our overuse of information technology: video games, television, digital watches, calculators, and computers. Information technology feeds us information without requiring us to think about it and let us perform operations without un...\n\nQ: What was the employee's problem?", "options": ["She couldn't operate the cash register.", "She forgot to count change.", "She couldn't solve simple math problems.", "She was in need of coins for customer."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1030, "question": "Some kinds of mental skills naturally decrease as people get older. Yet research seems to show that some training can improve such skills. A recently published study also appears to demonstrate that the good effects of training can last for many years after that training has ended. Researchers at Johns Hopkins University in Maryland wanted to learn how long memory and thinking skills would last in older people who trained to keep them. The people were part of the ten-year research project. They were taught methods meant to improve their memory, thinking and ability to perform everyday tasks. More than 2,800 volunteered for the study called ACTIVE - short for Advanced (Cognitive) Training for Independent and Vital Elderly. Most studied when they were more than 70 years old. The volunteers t...\n\nQ: What can be inferred from the passage?", "options": ["There were four groups being trained.", "The old people trained can remember words better.", "The second and third group improved their skills better than the first one.", "The research showed that the effect of the training could absolutely last 10 years."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1790, "question": "It's wonderful to go to another country, complete a volunteer project and feel that you really have a positive influence. But how can you become an international volunteer? * Plan practically. Contact the organization a few months before leaving and find out if there are materials which are rare and hard to attain for the project. What you often consider plentiful here, such as nails or hammers, is in great need in other parts of the world. * Do the project together, not on your own. You are a guest in the community. The most successful result is not that you build something and walk away, but that you and the community build something as a team. Share skills and build together. * Be flexible. Not everything is going to happen as planned. Often the other country doesn't have the right tool...\n\nQ: According to the author, volunteer will  _  .", "options": ["reduce challenge in the world", "determine the future of a volunteer", "change a person's opinion of the world", "benefit volunteers most in their learning"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1537, "question": "When I left my bag on a train, I lost my most precious possession, a small framed photograph of my great grandparents, Emily and Gordon Baker. The frame was made of silver, with an elegant flower design in one corner. The photograph was taken in March 1939 on their wedding day. Emily looked very happy, and Gordon looked rather alarmed. A few months later, he was killed in action in North Africa. I received the photograph when my aunt Mabel died. I'm a student at Edinburgh University and I live in an old Edwardian house. At the end of last term, I packed a large bag and a small bag and set off for London, where I was planning to catch the Eurostar train to Paris. Minutes after getting off the train at Kings Cross Station, I realized that I'd left the small bag in the overhead luggage rack. ...\n\nQ: Which of the statement about the author is not wrong?", "options": ["He left the photo on a train and never got it back.", "He put the photo in a small bag and left it on a train.", "He left the photo on the Eurostar and ran back to get it.", "He left the photo at his old Edwardian house in Edinburgh"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 142, "question": "In 1947 a group of famous people from the art world headed by an Austrian conductor decided to hold an intemational festival of music,dance and theatre in Edinburgh. The idea was to reunite Europe after the Second World War. At the same time, the \"Fringe\" appeared as a challenge to the official festival.Eight theatre groups turned up uninvited in 1947,in the belief that everyone should have the right to perform,and they did so in a public house disused for years. Soon,groups of studentsfirstly from Edinburgh University, and later from the universities of Oxford and Cambridge,Durham and Birmingham were making the journey to the Scottish capital each summer to perform theatre by little-known writers of plays in small church halls to the people of Edinburgh. Today the \"Fringe\",once less recog...\n\nQ: Why did some uninvited theatre groups come to  Edinburgh in 1947?", "options": ["They owned a public house there.", "They came to take up a challenge.", "They thought they were also famous.", "They wanted to take part in the festival."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3043, "question": "If you want to pay a visit to Iceland, you'll enter a whole new region of experience. You'll discover original nature as you've never seen it before. The freedom to wander in the city or the wilds as you please is the key to the Iceland experience. Reykjavik, the capital of Iceland, is just a part of the Icelandic experience with its midnight sun or the magical landscapes mixed with ice and fire. Reykjavik has a population of around 170,000 and offers an interesting mix of culture and local village roots. Old accounts say the ancient gods themselves guided Iceland's first settler to make his home in Reykjavik. He named the place Reykjavik (Steamy Bay)after the geothermal steam he saw, which today heats homes and outdoor swimming pools throughout the city, a pollution-free energy source tha...\n\nQ: It can be learned from the passage the Reykiavik_.", "options": ["was named by the ancient gods.", "was named by Iceland's first settler.", "got its name from the visitors.", "was named after Iceland's first settler."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2226, "question": "A Day of Design Sunday, June 27,2010 9 a. m. ~ 4 p. m. Thomas College Student Center Join us for a free day of fun! A Day of Design will encourage those interested in flowers and design to get in touch with their creative side and get some tips from the experts - Jeff and Scott. Pleas see the schedule below for details about this wonderful opportunity! 9:00 a.m. - 10:30 a.m. Registration for the day runs from 9 a.m. in the Student Center. Later guests will take a tour of the Thomas College campus before the day's events. 10:30 a. m. ~ 12:00 p. m. Jeff and Scott will design more than a dozen arrangements in a variety of sizes and colors and auction will be held and guests will have the opportunity to bid on the flower arrangements. 12:00 p. m. ~ 1:00 p. m. A delightful boxed lunch will be s...\n\nQ: When will an auction be held?", "options": ["9:00 a.m. ~ 10:30 a.m.", "10:30 a.m. ~ 12:00 p.m.", "1:00 p.m. ~ 3:00 p. m.", "3:00 p. m. ~ 4:00 p. m."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1753, "question": "As winter gives way to spring, students feel like taking outdoor activities. However, do remember that accidents can happen, such as the one that happened at Taihu Lake several weeks ago. Four students from Shanghai were killed and several were injured. There were several reasons for the accident, but if the students had worn life jackets, it would have made a big difference. Therefore, it is important to take steps to avoid accidents before going on trips whether on land or water. Here are some steps: Make sure you are physically fit for any activities. You need energy for hiking or boating after a long inactive winter. Research your route . Check the weather report so you can pack the correct things so that an unexpected downpour or high winds won't destroy your day. If you are visiting ...\n\nQ: Which of the following can be used as the best title?", "options": ["Be Well Prepared for Outdoor Activities.", "Pay Attention to Unexpected Accidents.", "Do Take Outdoor Activities in a Group.", "Be Sure to Avoid Being Injured When Traveling."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1644, "question": "NEW ORLEANS --A two-story, 1,500-ton and 16,000-square foot school built in 1879 is being moved about 300 yards to make way for the new University Medical Center in MidCity. The school' s relocation is marked as the largest structure ever to be moved in Louisiana and one of the top-ten heaviest in America.Officials originally had planned to _ the McDonogh No.11 School, but agreed to move the historic building at the city's request. The school is being moved on a platform of steel beams put under the schoolhouse floor, then set on 38 remote-controlled power dollies made mobile by 300 tires.The school is creeping forward on a short stay that will take about two days to move it about 300 yards. State officials said the operation shows how closely the state and city leaders are working toprese...\n\nQ: Cancienne and his team made no money from the project because   _  .", "options": ["it' s a chance for them to do something for the state", "the company is famous for doing volunteer work", "the state is short of money to cover the cost", "it' s easy for them to complete the project"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 187, "question": "There are a number of different ways to study a language, each of which has advantages and disadvantages. You may find a combination of these is a best choice for you. If you can find a course in the language you want to learn in your country, this is quite a good way to study. A variety of courses are usually available, including part-time and full-time courses. If you look around, you can probably find a course that suits your needs. The main advantage of such courses is that you'll have a teacher to provide you with instructions, support and with whom to practice your language. You will also be studying with others who are at more or less the same level and you can exchange ideas with them and help one another. One choice is to study a language in a country where it's spoken. There are ...\n\nQ: What can we learn from this passage?    _", "options": ["Studying abroad is the only good way to study English.", "All the online courses are very easy to study.", "If you study a language in your own country, you can study with more partners of the same level.", "You can get any job you like after studying abroad."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 478, "question": "Friends play an important role in our lives, and although we can't be more familiar with the fact of friendship, we often don't clearly understand how we make friends, especially with Americans. Here are some pieces of advice on making friends with Americans: 1. Visiting places Americans enjoy: parties, churches, restaurants, parks and sports clubs. 2. Be willing to take the first step. Don't wait for them to get close to you. Americans in China may not know you speak English. They may be uncomfortable if they can't speak your language. 3. Use small talks to open the conversation. Ask them where they're from, why they come to China, etc. . Remember: Be careful not to ask personal questions about age, salary and so on. 4. Show an interest in their culture, their country or their job. Americ...\n\nQ: What should you say when meeting an American for the first time?", "options": ["What's your age?", "How much do you get in a month?", "Nice to meet you! Are you from America?", "Let's get together sometime. I want to ask you some questions."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 151, "question": "As the train approached the seaside town where I was going to spend my holiday, I went into the corridor to stretch my legs.I stayed there for a short while,breathing in the fresh air and exchanging a few words with one of the passengers,whom I had met earlier on the station platform. When I turned to go back to my seat,I happened to glance into the compartment next to mine.Sitting there was a man who many years before had been my neighbor.He was a great talker, I remembered;it used to take hours to get away from him once he began talking.I was not at all sorry when he went to live in another part of London.We had not met since then,nor did I wish to meet him now, when my holiday was about to begin. Luckily at that moment he was much too busy talking to the man opposite him to have the cha...\n\nQ: Whom did the writer see in the compartment next to his?", "options": ["One of his former neighbors.", "One of his old friends.", "One of his s.", "One whom he wanted to see."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 282, "question": "Chinese New Year celebrations, also known as the Spring Festival start on the 23rd day of the 12th lunar month of the Chinese calendar, and end on the 15th day of the first lunar month in the following year in the Chinese calendar. Chinese New Year's Day's date is calculated according to the Chinese lunar calendar. In 2015 it's Thursday, February 19. Many people clean their homes to welcome the Spring Festival. They put up the red posters with poetic verses on it to their doors, Chinese New Year pictures on their walls, and decorate their homes with red lanterns. It is also a time to reunite with s so many people visit their families at this time of the year. In the evening of the Spring Festival Eve, many people set off fireworks and firecrackers, hoping to cast away any bad luck and brin...\n\nQ: The original purpose of the red posters is", "options": ["to show some wonderful poems to others", "to decorate the house with bright color1s", "to drive the evils away from their homes", "to welcome friends and s warmly"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2815, "question": "The idea of light pollution has developed with the increase of lights in cities. In many areas, this light makes it difficult or impossible to observe stars and planets in the night sky. There are a number of reasons why light pollution is important. One has become clear at the Mount Wilson Observatory near Los Angeles, California. Today, light from Los Angeles makes the night sky above Mount Wilson very bright. It is no longer an important reasearch center because of light pollution. Light pollution threatens to reduce the scientific value of research telescoples in other important observatories. They include Lick Observatory near San Jose, California and Yerkes Observatory near Chicago, Illionis. Light pollution is the result of wasted energy. Bright light that shines into the sky is not...\n\nQ: Light pollution usually occurs  _  .", "options": ["in cities", "in the country", "in wild areas", "in developing countries"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1398, "question": "An air of anxious uncertainty spread throughout the small Indian camp as the sun dawned that morning. Some braves gathered beside a smoking campfire. Murmuring sounds could be heard as they talked quietly. Women nervously performed their domestic tasks, preparing a small meal. Several sad, old men sat mute, their morale very low. The camp was pitched at the edge of a deep valley--so deep that one could barely see the calm water at the bottom. The Indians had been taken by surprise and were surrounded and attacked by enemy forces. They fought bravely, but they were degraded by defeat. Their homes were destroyed. Those who had survived had been pursued by the enemy. The chase had lasted for days. Persuaded by their leaders to press on, they had made a wrong turn. Their _ journey ended at the...\n\nQ: When some young braves reported seeing a stone bridge across the valley, most of the Indians in the camp  _  .", "options": ["felt much relieved at the report.", "were excited by the report.", "didn't trust the report.", "believed the report."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1445, "question": "Anyone who doubts that children are born with a healthy amount of ambition need spend only a few minutes with a baby eagerly learning to walk. No matter how many times the little ones stumble in their first efforts, most keep on trying, determined to master their amazing new skill. It is only several years later, many psychologists and teachers agree, that a good number of kids seem to lose their natural drive to succeed. For the parents of such kids, whose own ambition is often tied to their children's success, it can be a painful experience. Figuring out why _ is the first step. Assuming that a kid doesn't suffer from a learning disability, or isn't involved in some family crisis at home, many educators attribute a sudden lack of motivation to a fear of failure or classmate pressure. \"Ev...\n\nQ: All the following can contribute to a sudden lack of ambition EXCEPT  _  .", "options": ["learning disability", "classmate pressure", "emphasis on testing", "extracurricular activities"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2876, "question": "A 56-year-old Canadian man who left home after his business went bankrupt completed an 11-year walk around the world on Sunday, and told a crowd of well-wishers his new goal was to promote peace. Jean Beliveau -- who arrived to a hero's welcome in Montreal from loved ones, lawmakers and supporters -- said his \"real aim \" was to advise Canada and other governments to build \"ministries of peace.\" \"We are all different, and that is what is beautiful about life on Earth -- our different color1s, different beliefs, different political systems,\" he said. \"Those are all musical notes... we must create harmony from them, create a common tune,\" an emotional Beliveau told the crowd gathering at city hall in the old part of the city. Beliveau left Montreal on the day of his 45th birthday -- August 18...\n\nQ: Beliveau said that his new goal is to   _  .", "options": ["forget his pain", "promote world peace", "create a common belief", "have a good rest"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 575, "question": "There are three main forms of public transport in Singapore--trains,buses and taxis. TRAINS Trains run from 6:00 am to midnight. Single trip tickets start at 80 cents. If you buy an EZ-Link card for $ 15,you can ride the trains and buses as you like. If you need more infor-mation, just call Train Station at 6222 5165. BUSES There are several bus services in Singapore and fares start at 80 cents. Be sure always to ask the driver the cost of your ticket as he can't give change. If you need help,just call Tran-sit Link at 1800 767 4333. TAXIS There are three main taxi companies--City Cab (6552 2222),Comfort (6552 1111) and Tibs (6552 8888). Booking can also be easy by calling the numbers listed above. RENTAL CARS Driving in Singapore is a pleasure and if you like to travel at your own pace,re...\n\nQ: With an EZ-Link card, you can take_.", "options": ["only trains", "both buses and trains", "only rental cars", "both buses and taxis"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3365, "question": "One day, I was studying at home . Suddenly, there was a loud noise. I went out of my house to see what had happened . What I saw made me scared. A building in my neighborhood was on fire. Some people were using water to put out the fire; others were rushing towards the building to help put out the fire. The building had three floors. The fire started on the first floor. Soon, it spread to the second floor. There were some people on the second floor at that time. Their lives were in danger. A few people jumped out of the window. Luckily, they only got small injuries. Those who were still on the second floor were just crying for help. The people outside didn't know how to help the people inside to get out. Firefighters arrived at last. They fought the fire bravely. Water pipes were used and ...\n\nQ: _  was on fire.", "options": ["The author's room", "A ladder", "A building in the author's neighborhood", "Only the second floor of the building"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3276, "question": "Throughout life,change is the only thing that seems constant.Change has come to my 1ife many ways,in myself,and in my surroundings.At the same time,some things stay the same.This is when traditions are formed.I am often reminded of this by the photograph that sits by my bed. It all began with a kiss on my very first day of school.I remember dancing around the mirror,watching as my dark blue dress created a teacup around my waist.I admired the little ruffle of my shirt collar and how it matched perfectly with the trim at the bottom of my dress.I knew I would be the envy of all my classmates. But somehow,something was missing.I reached under my bed for the large box of bows ,in every color1 imaginable,that I was famous for.I picked out a white one that would match my shirt and carefully ran ...\n\nQ: Why did the author look for bows according to Paras 2 and 3 ?", "options": ["Because her mother liked bows very much.", "Because she was famous for making bows.", "Because her favorite bow was missing.", "Because she wanted to look perfect."], "answer": 3}]